

PHONE: 317-903-4622

EMAIL: adam31kern@gmail.com
PORTFOLIO: https://adam-kern.github.io/

SUMMARY:

Professional with 3 years of experience in technology, communications and digital strategy with a unique ability to utilize website and data management skills to drive results as a Salesforce Administrator. Bilingual graduate of Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder program with Salesforce Administrator certification and 65 Trailhead badges.

SKILLS AND CERTIFICATIONS:

Salesforce Administrator Certification Firebase, Github, Heroku Google Adwords Certification

JavaScript Node Facebook and Twitter Ads Manager

React Bootstrap, Reactstrap, Material Google Analytics

Angular Google Suite Shopify and e-commerce

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Web Director and Press Secretary - Indiana House of Representatives - (Indianapolis, IN)

2018 - Present

- Managed Indiana House of Representative websites ensuring content is current and engaging
- Coordinated media relations for 14 state representatives, wrote over 50 press releases and columns and arranged interviews with local and national news outlets including the Associated Press and Fox News
- Created and executed online legislative surveys, collecting over 200,000 results from Hoosier households
- Designed 60 individualized reports for representatives illustrating results from mail and online survey
- Trained over 15 government staff to use the House of Representative website and CMS

Account Executive - Harris Media LLC - (Austin, TX)

2016 - 2018

- Directed digital marketing campaign for Bob Stefanowski resulting in the first ever primary win for a candidate petitioning their way onto the gubernatorial ballot in Connecticut
- Executed a digital fundraising campaign that raised \$75,000 in 7 days using email and social media
- Project management experience pushing multiple website design and business development projects forward, while simultaneously managing accounts and campaigns for existing clients
- Oversaw the design of multiple video projects including a video that received over 2,000,000 views

Marketing Intern - Cobra Moto LLC - (Hillsdale, MI)

2015 - 2016

- Managed company's website, social media, and digital accounts
- Doubled Cobra Moto's video channel subscribers for Facebook and YouTube

EDUCATION:

Salesforce and Deloitte Pathfinder Program - Administrator Certification

2019 - Present

- Salesforce and Deloitte joint program to build Salesforce Administrator and business soft skills providing 100+ hours of Salesforce technical training
- Advanced technical skills include: data management (incl. data modeling, security and data access), automation using workflow rules and process builder, and reports / dashboards

Eleven Fifty Academy

2019

- Javascript Immersive Program
- · Created a portfolio, React website and database, and Angular website and database

Hillsdale College, Bachelor of Arts, American Studies and Spanish

2012 - 2016

- Magna cum Laude with Departmental Honors 3.65 GPA
- Center for Cultural Studies Study Abroad Seville, Spain
- · Sigma Chi International Fraternity

PERSONAL:

Leadership Council Member - The Philos Project

2018 - Present

• Traveled to New York City, Poland, Israel, and Jordan, attended seminars, and collaborated on entrepreneurial projects focused on social entrepreneurship and humanitarian relief work in the Middle East

Big Brothers Big Sisters Program Coordinator

2014 - 2016

• Oversaw program operations and recruited at least 5 new volunteers each semester

Eagle Scout

• Led workers in a project to restore a courtyard of a homeless shelter in downtown Indianapolis

2008